♪♪（太鼓）
（ナルト）『尾獣数え唄』
はじまり　はじまり！
for some reason the moon is one size larger tonight
konya no tsuki wa nazeka hitomawari ookikute
♪♪「一つ　人より」
♪♪「居眠り守鶴」
♪♪「二つ　ファイヤー
燃えてる又旅」
it's shining brighter than it usually does
itsumo yori akaruku terasu
♪♪「三つ　水なら」
I trudge along the road home with my shoulders hunched
senaka wo marumete tobotobo kaeru michi
♪♪「任せろ　磯撫」
♪♪「四つ　溶岩
あついぜ孫悟空」
at any time I will always have a friend
donna toki mo mikata wa iru
♪♪「五つ
いつでも」
without saying a word, it's all right to cry
nani mo iwazu naketara ii ne
♪♪「駆け足
穆王」
♪♪「六つ
無理せず」
♪♪「アワてず
犀犬」
once my tears dry, it will all be over
namida ga karetara owari
♪♪「七つ　ナナフシ
空飛ぶ重明」
♪♪「八つ　やっぱり」
I need to become stronger...
motto boku ga tsuyoku naranakya
♪♪「ウィーだぜ　牛鬼」
♪♪「九つ
ココンと」
sorrow is the first step towards independence
kanashimi wa jiritsu he no ippo
♪♪「最強
九喇嘛」
♪♪「とうとうそろった　尾獣の仲間」
♪♪「ちょい　ムズだけどいい名前」
how many times do I have to get hurt to forget the pain?
nando kizutsukeba itami wo wasureru
♪♪「みんな　立派な名前だね」
when I bleed red, I'm reminded of life
akai chi wo nagaseba inochi wo omoidasu sa
♪♪「みんな　すてきな名前だね」
みんなも　九喇嘛と
仲間たちの名前→
I collapse on the road with my arms and legs spread out
michi ni taore dainoji ni
覚えてくれってばよ！
I look up at the sky and think
sora wo miagete omou
true loneliness is someone without a past
shin no kodoku to wa kako no nai mono
someone who only knows the present
ima shika shiranu mono
Tailed Beast Counting Song!
All right, here we go!
One, "sleep is better than humans,"
says Shukaku
Two, burning in fire, Matatabi
Three, leave the water to Isobu
Four, hot as lava, Son Goku
Five, always on the run, Kokuo
Six, taking it easy and
not in a hurry, Saiken
Seven, the flying leaf insect,
Chomei
Eight, "Yeah!" is all it needs,
Gyuki
Nine, "ko-kon" cries
the mighty Kurama
All the Tailed Beasts have
finally come together
They're a little hard,
but they're nice names
They're all splendid names
They're all wonderful names
Hey everyone!
Please try to learn Kurama
and the others' names, okay?
The Risks of the Reanimation Jutsu
You think you can beat me
with Hashirama's will?
（マダラ）柱間が死んで残した
その意志とやらで→
俺に勝てると？
Power is not will.
Power is only the ability
to make things happen.
（マダラ）力とは　意志ではなく
物質の起こす事象のことだ。
You're wrong!
The will of the dead
shows its power
（綱手）違う！　死者の意志が→
in those they left behind!
残された者を突き動かし
力を現す！
I used that will to develop
my Medical Ninjutsu.
私の作った医療忍術も
その意志から生まれ→
From there, Medic Ninja and
Medical Laws were established!
医療忍者と掟が構築された！
Rule One! A Medic Ninja must
never give up on treatment
第一項　医療忍者は決して
隊員の命　尽きるまで→
until their patient's dying breath.
治療を諦めてはならない！
Rule Two! A Medic Ninja must
never go to the frontlines!
第二項　医療忍者は決して
最前線に立ってはならない！
Rule Three!
A Medic Ninja should always be
第三項　医療忍者は決して
小隊のなかで→
the last of their platoon to die!
最後まで死んではならない！
This is what I teach my students.
弟子たちに教えたのは
ここまでだ。
But there is actually
one more rule...
だが　掟はもうひとつある。
Rule Four!
A Medic Ninja who masters
第四項　忍法　創造再生→
the Ninja Art of Mitotic Regeneration,
the 100 Healings...
百豪の術を極めし
医療忍者のみ→
may break the first three rules!
上記の掟を破棄できる！
（メイ）なっ！
The 100 Healings Jutsu?
百豪の術だと？
I've never heard of it.
聞いたこともない。
It's a Forbidden Jutsu that
applies only to me.
私だけの禁術…。
Which means,
I am the only Medic Ninja
allowed to battle!
つまり　私だけは
戦えるってことだ！
The Particle Style Jutsu may
have dissipated the pollen...
花粉は　塵遁で消し飛んだが→
But adding one Medic Ninja
won't make any difference...
医療忍者が　１人増えたところで。
Four wasn't working,
so we'll try five!
４人でダメなら　５人でいく。
Don't you dare think
I'm an ordinary Medic Ninja!
私をただの医療忍者だと
思うなよ！
She's not as fast as the Raikage...
《スピードは　雷影以下》
Let's go!
（エー）いくぞ！
But her power is greater than his!
《パワーは　雷影以上か》
Fire Style...
火遁　豪火滅失！
Majestic Demolisher Flame!
Water Style: Water Pillar!
《水遁　水陣柱！
Water Style!
Water Dragon Missile!
水遁　水龍弾！》
Weighted Boulder!
Lateral Bolt of Pain! Chop!
《オオノキ：加重岩！》
《エー：雷虐水平チョップ！》
I admit...
You're not weak, woman.
確かに　か弱い女ではないな。
However...
だが…。
If you step in and die here,
お前が　でしゃばり死ねば
他の影も終わりだぞ。
all the other Kage will die.
Since you're the only one
who can heal them.
回復役は
貴様だけのようだしな。
That's if I die.
それは　私が死ねばの話だ。
Hashirama...
I don't know what
you left behind...
柱間…　お前が
何を残したかは知らんが…。
But this falls far short
of your abilities.
この程度…
お前には　遠く及ばん…。
If you were going to let
your underlings take over,
どうせ　下っ端に
引き継がせるなら→
you should have taught them
how to resurrect you too...
俺のように　復活のやり方でも
教えておくべきだったな…。
All that's left of you is
the life force of your cells
お前が死んで残ったものは→
俺に　へばりつく
細胞の生命力でしかない。
that cling to me.
All that's left of
my little brother is
弟が死んで残ったものは→
the Visual Prowess of his eyes,
which are now mine.
俺の両眼の瞳術しかない。
That's why...
だから…。
I said you're wrong!
だから　違うと言っている！
The only thing that is
passed down...
引き継がれるものが
あるとすれば…。
is hatred.
憎しみだけだ。
What?!
（ダン）何！？　あのマダラが
穢土転生されたのか！？
Madara was brought back
with the Reanimation?
Now that the real Madara
showed up,
（チョウザ）本物のマダラが
出てきた以上→
the Five Kage had to step in!
五影も　悠長に構えては
いられなくなりました。
As the Hokage, Lady Tsunade
has joined the battle as well.
火影として　綱手様も
応戦に出られています。
Tsunade is the Hokage?!
（ダン）綱手が火影！？
あいつ　火影になったのか？
She became the Hokage?!
Did I neglect to tell you?
（チョウザ）話してませんでしたっけ？
Well, Lady Tsunade went through
quite a lot after your passing...
まあ　綱手様も→
あなたが亡くなられてから
いろいろ　ありましたが…。
But in the end, it just showed
how much she cared about you.
結局は
あなたを慕っていましたから…。
Tsunade...
綱手…。
There's no way Lady Tsunade
will lose!
綱手様が
負けるわけありませんよ！
That's why she is
the sole surviving member
だからこそ　三忍の中で→
of the Legendary Sannin!
唯一　あの歳まで
生きてらっしゃる！
You're already dead!
《綱手：お前は死んでいる！
So don't spread any more hate!
だから　これ以上
憎しみを　ばらまかないでくれ…》
Kazekage! Now!
風影　今だ！
Grand Sand Mausoleum!
（我愛羅）砂漠層大葬！
He's been sealed!
（我愛羅）封印した！
よし！
All right!
The one you sealed away
is a Wood Style Clone
お前たちが閉じ込めたのは→
that Hashirama used to use.
柱間が使っていた　木遁分身だ。
It is well made...
よく出来ていてな…。
My Visual Prowess made me the only shinobi
who was able to see the ruse...
かつて　敵として
これを見抜けたのは→
俺だけだった…。
in the past.
この瞳力でな。
さて…。
Now then...
It's over for the rest of you Kage...
これで　他の影も終わりだな。
Don't underestimate Madara!
（ダン）マダラをナメたら　ダメだ！
The only way to stop Madara
is to stop
やつを止めるには→
the one who cast
the Reanimation.
大本にいる穢土転生の術者を
止めるしかない！
Is Madara...
that powerful a shinobi?
マダラとは
それほどの忍なのですか？
Even against the Five Kage
facing him now?
こちらは　五影で
相手をしているというのに。
Aside from the late First Hokage...
おそらく
マダラと戦って　勝てる忍は…。
there is no one right now
who can defeat Madara in battle...
今は亡き
初代火影様をおいて　他にない。
My guard and my barrier sustainer
should stay here.
俺の見張り役と　結界役以外は→
Everyone else should be going after
the caster of the Reanimation Jutsu!
すぐに　穢土転生の術者捜索に
回したほうがいい！
How is HQ dealing with this?
本部の対応は　どうなっている！
Every effort is being made,
もちろん　全力でやってますが→
but there's been no concrete intel...
これといった情報はなくて…。
Don't die... Tsunade!
《死ぬなよ…　綱手》
Summoning Jutsu!
《イタチ：口寄せの術！》
Damn it!
（サスケ）クソッ！
（イタチ）お前は　ここにいろ。
You stay here.
There, huh?
《あそこか…　つまらぬ結界だ》
What a useless barrier.
I'm impressed you were able
to pass through my barrier,
（カブト）僕の結界を通り抜け
よく　ここがわかったね。
and find this place.
When you were controlling me,
お前に操られている間→
I was able to pinpoint where
your chakra was coming from.
お前のチャクラが
どこから来ているかは→
はっきり感じていた。
これも　術のリスクだ。
That's another risk of this jutsu.
Though you won't need to
remember that for next time.
覚えておく必要は
もう　ないがな。
Thanks for the tip.
（カブト）勉強になったよ。
I didn't expect any shinobi
to counter this jutsu,
この術をはね除けられるような
忍は　まずいないから→
so I didn't even worry about it.
そういう心配は
していなかったからね。
By the way, there's something
I'd like you to know as well.
ああ　代わりに覚えておいて
ほしいことがあるんだ。
This Reanimation Jutsu
will not come undone
この穢土転生の術は
僕を殺しても止まらないけど→
even if you kill me.
But I am the only one
who can stop it.
この術を止められるのは
僕しかいない。　つまり→
In other words...
You can't kill me.
キミは　僕を殺せないのさ。
If I die, you'll never be able
to stop this jutsu.
僕が死ねば　二度と　この術を
止めることができなくなる。
クククク…　アハハハハハ！
I guess my luck
hasn't run out yet!
運が回ってきたどころじゃ
ないみたいだね！　この僕。
Things are not always as
we wish them to be, damn it!
思うようにはいかないものだ。
まったく。
I caught up to you!
追いついたぞ。
こんなところで　いったい…。
What the hell are you doing here?
Is that... Orochimaru?
大蛇丸…　なのか？
You're a little off...
（カブト）クク…　少し違う。
That voice...
その声は　カブト！
Kabuto!
It's perfect timing that my compensation
for participating in this war
戦争協力の見返りが
このタイミングで　自ら→
would show up, on his own,
at this particular moment...
僕の目の前に来ちゃうとはね。
I am so lucky.
ラッキーだよ。
What are you talking about?
どういう意味だ？
What are you both doing here?
なぜ　お前たちが
こんなところで？
It's rather complicated...
（カブト）ややこしい状況だよね。
僕が簡単に説明しようか。
Let me try to explain.
Go ahead.
説明していろ。
And in the meantime,
I'll stop the Reanimation.
そのスキに
穢土転生は止めさせてもらう。
This jutsu has neither
risks nor weaknesses.
（カブト）この術に弱点はない。
リスクもない。　イタチ…　キミのほうには
それを説明したいんだけど。
I want you to understand
that Itachi.
Even if you do make a move,
とにかく　キミが動くにも→
I doubt Sasuke will just
sit back and watch.
サスケ君が　おとなしく
していないと思うけどね。
If you rush, you may not succeed,
焦ると止められるものも
止められないかもよ。
even if it were possible,
conversely...
逆に。
Kabuto, answer my question!
カブト！　質問に答えろ！
I guess I have to tell you,
after all.
（カブト）結局
話さないとダメみたいだね。
I mean, while you were asleep
そりゃそうだよね　サスケ君。
from having your brother's eyes
transplanted into you...
キミが　お兄さんの眼を移植して
寝ている間に→
something drastic happened
in our world.
世界は　とんでもないことに
なっているんだもんね。
Tobi started the war, huh?
トビが戦争を仕掛けたんだな。
So you know a little.
少しは知ってるんだ。
まぁ　そうだよね。
Yes, that's true...
The Fourth Great Ninja War...
第四次忍界大戦。
Tobi and I are at war
with the coalition
トビと僕は　火の国　風の国
水の国　土の国→
of the Nations of Fire, Wind,
Water, Earth and Lightning...
雷の国。　この五大国が
協力して作り上げた→
The Allied Shinobi Force.
忍連合を相手に戦っている。
There's no way you two can fight
五大国相手に　お前たちだけで
戦えるはずがないだろう！
against the Five Great Nations!
Oh, but we can...
それが戦えるんだなぁ！
With a hundred thousand
mass-produced White Zetsu!
（カブト）白いほうの
ゼツの量産型が１０万体。
And the reanimated battalion
that I created...
そして　僕が生み出した
穢土転生の部隊。
Kinkaku and Ginkaku!
金角　銀角。
The former members of
霧隠れ忍刀七人衆の　前任者たち。
the Seven Ninja Swords
Men of the Mist!
The Second Tsuchikage...
二代目土影。
The Third Raikage...
三代目雷影。
The Second Mizukage...
二代目水影。
The Fourth Kazekage...
四代目風影。
And Madara Uchiha...
そして　うちはマダラ。
I don't have time to mention
all the names.
名前を挙げていったら　キリがない。
Your brother over there is
also one of the ones I reanimated.
そこにいる　キミのお兄さんも→
穢土転生で　よみがえった一人さ。
Well?
どう？　意外と僕もやるでしょ？
Not too shabby, huh?
Although Madara Uchiha
planned everything.
もっとも　すべては
うちはマダラの計画なんだけどね。
What do you mean?
どういうことだ？
Like you two,
he hated the Shinobi World.
（カブト）キミたちと同じさ。
忍世界への恨み。
And so, he came up
with Project Tsuki no Me.
そのために彼は
月の眼計画を立てた。
Project Tsuki no Me?
月の眼計画？
A plan to cast a powerful genjutsu
over the entire world
十尾を使って　この地上全体に
巨大な幻術をかけるのさ。
using the Ten Tails.
To control the world.
そして　この地上を支配する。
For that,
we need Naruto's Nine Tails
そのために　ナルト君の九尾と→
and Killer Bee's Eight Tails.
キラービーの八尾が
どうしても必要なのさ。
And just about now...
今頃　それを手に入れるために→
Madara is causing a ruckus
on the battlefield in order to get them.
マダラは戦場を
暴れ回っているんじゃないかな。
Now then, who's next...?
さて…　次は　どいつにするかな。
ぬお～っ！
おりゃ～！
How can you move?
（マダラ）なぜ　お前が動ける？
Like I told you, I'm different!
だから　私は違うと言ったはずだ。
Regeneration without weaving signs...
So that's the real power of your jutsu
mentioned in Rule Four.
（マダラ）印を使わぬ再生体…　そうか。
それが　第四項の
お前の術の能力というわけか。
It's just like Hashirama's power.
柱間の能力と同じだな。
I wanted to catch you off guard
with this, but...
これで　スキを
作ったつもりだったんだがな。
You can't kill me with
my own jutsu.
俺の術で　俺をやれるか。
I can kill you, with my jutsu!
《オオノキ：わしの術ならやれる！》
All right!
よ～し！
Have you gone senile, Ohnoki?
The Rinnegan can absorb
all jutsu.
（マダラ）ボケたか？　オオノキ。
輪廻眼は
すべての術を　吸収する。
Ninjutsu like that will
not work against me!
俺に　その手の忍術は通用しない。
To kill me, you need to hit me
hard physically and seal me.
俺をやるなら　直に殴り倒し→
You know that.
封印するしかないと
わかっているだろう？
My Particle Style grazed
your chest earlier...
さっきは　わしの塵遁で
お前の胸をかすめた。
There's no way that the Atomic
Dismantling Jutsu didn't work!
原界剥離の術が
通じぬはずがない！
Oh that...
I just wanted to show you
all Hashirama's face.
あれか…。　あれは　柱間の顔を
お前らに見せつけたくなってな。
I wanted to reduce your morale...
お前らの士気を
下げてやるつもりだったんだが→
But it seems it had the opposite effect...
It boosted your morale instead.
逆に士気を
上げてしまったようだな。
Let me ask you a question.
一つ　質問をする。
While it doesn't change the fact
that you outwitted us with
the Wood Style Clone...
木遁分身で　私たち５人を
出し抜いたことには→
But from another angle,
変わりはないが
見方を変えれば→
you could say we managed
to corner you
分身して身代わりを
出さなければならないほど→
into having to substitute
a clone for yourself.
追い詰められたとも言える。
Am I wrong?
違うか？
It is five against one, after all...
（マダラ）さすがに　５対１だからな。
Even if it is five-to-one,
we must win, no matter what.
５対１でも
勝たなければならないの。
Don't call it unfair!
In truth, it is a testament
to your might!
卑怯とは言わないでくださいよ。
それだけ　あなたの強さを
認めてあげてるってことですから。
You are Madara Uchiha!
（メイ）あなたは　うちはマダラです。
It's not unfair.
Five-to-one... It's just the right ratio
for playing games.
卑怯とは言わぬ。　５人で１人。
遊ぶには　ちょうどいい。
Now it's five-to-one.
これで　５対１だ。
Don't say this is unfair.
You are the Five Kage.
卑怯とは　ぬかすなよ。
お前らは五影だ。
So now I've got
a question for you...
さて　一つ質問をする。
Would you like these clones
to use Susano'o or not?
そいつら分身が
スサノオを使う　使わない→
Your choice.
どちらがいい？
So that's the story of the war...
ってのが　戦争の話。
But what is a Reanimation
like you doing here?
だが　どうして　穢土転生で
よみがえったあんたが→
Your intent to kill is real.
こんなところにいる？
あんたの殺気は本物だ。
The reason is simple...
I'm not under his control.
理由は簡単だ。
俺は　こいつに操られていない。
You're absolutely right.
I must hand it to you,
Itachi Uchiha.
（カブト）確かに　そのとおり。
さすが　うちはイタチだよね。
まさか　穢土転生の術に→
Imagine, overwriting
the Reanimation Jutsu
with your genjutsu...
自分の幻術を上書きするなんて
普通は考えつかない。
Normally, one wouldn't
even think of that.
Sorry, but I hate taking orders.
あいにく　俺は→
誰かに命令されるのが
嫌いなんでな。
Well, I agree with you there.
その点は　僕も同調する。
You haven't answered
all my questions!
まだ俺の質問に
すべて答えていない！
Just because you asked
doesn't mean
なんでも聞けば誰かが
答えてくれるって考えは→
you're going to get a reply.
いかがなもんかとは思うけど。
You haven't changed
from the days
まあ　アカデミーの頃から人気者の
キミらしい傾向だけどね。
when you were the popular one
at the Academy.
Meaning... I'm still forceful?
俺らしい傾向とは…
力ずくってことか？
Just kidding!
Looks like your big brother here...
冗談さ。
どうやらキミのお兄さんは…。
I came to kill you.
You heard him.
お前を殺しに来た。
らしいよ。
Reanimation... You got a hold
of a silly Forbidden Jutsu.
穢土転生…。
つまらぬ禁術を持ち出したな。
But you see,
thanks to this jutsu,
おやおや。　この術のおかげで
キミたちは→
you siblings get to have
a touching reunion.
感動の再会ができているのに。
I was hoping for
a little gratitude here.
少しは感謝してほしいな。
Reanimation can't control
the heart.
穢土転生は
心まで操れるわけじゃない。
You've desecrated souls
that were purified
お前は浄化した魂を冒涜し→
and continue to spread
unnecessary sadness and hate.
必要のない悲しみと憎しみを
ばらまき続けている。
Can you understand the pain
死者たちが戦う苦しみが
お前に　わかるか？
felt by the dead who
are forced to fight?
The pain of the living
is even greater.
生き残った者たちの
気持は　なおさらだ。
After finally getting over
the grief and sadness...
やっと乗り越えた
嘆きと悲しみを。
your jutsu has stirred
those feelings again!
お前の術は　ぶり返した。
Well...
I'm a little surprised...
へぇ～。　ちょっとビックリだな。
that someone who slaughtered
the entire Uchiha Clan
うちは一族を皆殺しにした
キミに→
has such a tender heart...
そんな優しい心があったとはね。
Does it mean you regret it?
それともキミが
それを後悔してるって話かな？
If so, I'm not interested.
Say whatever you want.
だったら僕には興味がないけど。
You die here.
何とでも言え。
ここでお前は終わりだ。
Sasuke...
You want to bring down Itachi,
サスケ君。
the bane of the Uchiha,
once again, don't you?
（カブト）キミはうちは一族の敵である
イタチを　また倒したい。
Since I brought him back
to this realm.
僕がこの世に
転生させちゃったからね。
In short, Itachi is a nuisance
to both you and myself.
つまりサスケ君と僕にとっての
今のイタチは邪魔な存在。
Well? Shall we team up and
take down Itachi together?
ということになるよね？
どうだろう。
ここは　一つ協力して→
このイタチを倒そうじゃないか。
We share the same power of
the snake and the same Master—
同じ蛇の力を持ち
同じ師を…。
I have no intention of calling
that thing my Master!
あれを師と呼ぶ気はない。
Besides, it seems like
you don't know anything, do you?
それにお前は
何も知らないようだな。
I chased Itachi all the way here
to talk to him.
俺は今　イタチと話をするために
ここまで追ってきた。
Well then... whose side
are you on right now?
なら　キミは今　どっちの味方だい？
Why?!
He's just like Orochimaru!
なぜだ！？
こいつは大蛇丸と同じ。
Which means he's my enemy!
And right now,
he's your enemy too, right?!
だとしたら　俺の敵だ！
そして今は
あんたの敵でもあるんだろ！？
All right, we'll talk later.
わかった。　話は　あとでしてやる。
First things first,
let's take him down.
代わりに　まずは　こいつを倒す。
But don't kill him.
ただし　殺すな。
If you kill the caster
of the Reanimation,
the jutsu can never
be undone.
（イタチ）穢土転生の術者を
殺してしまっては→
術は永久に解けない。
We'll put him under
my Tsukuyomi,
まずはそいつを
俺の月読にかけ→
then we'll make him tell us
how to stop this jutsu.
その術を止める方法を聞き出す。
And while he's still under
the Tsukuyomi,
そして　月読にはめたまま
こいつを俺が操り→
I'll control him and...
I'll break this jutsu.
俺が　この術を解く。
Thanks for the play-by-play.
流暢に僕の倒し方を
しゃべってくれちゃって。
I hope it goes as smoothly
as you say.
口で言うほど
うまくいけばいいけど→
But I told you earlier,
this jutsu has neither weakness
nor risks—
この術には
弱点もリスクもないって　さっき…。
Every jutsu has a weakness.
（イタチ）どんな術にも
弱点となる穴がある。
This jutsu's weakness and risk...
ん？
（イタチ）この術の弱点とリスクは…。
is my existence!
この俺の存在だ。
Itachi... you've kept lying to me,
イタチ。　あんたはいつも俺に→
telling me "next time"
or "later," then you died on me...
「今度だ　あとでだ」と
ウソをつき　あげく死んだ。
So this time for sure...
I'm holding you to
your promise.
だから　今度こそ
約束は守ってもらう。
They say you take
your personality to the grave.
性格は死ぬまで変わらないが
俺は一度死んでいる。
Well, I've already died once.
I intend to honor it.
そのつもりだ。
The estranged brothers
come together to gang up on me?
兄弟で　僕を仲間はずれですか。
How fun!
おもしろい。
gozen reiji akari kieta machi
At midnight, in a city where the lights are out
koyoi wa odore tipsy night
I'm going to dance tonight Tipsy Night
tsukiakari mo todokanu basho ni wa
In a place where the moonlight doesn't reach
kodoku sae mo utau machi ga aru
There's a city that brings loneliness
kuruisou na furuesou na itami dake ga
There's only a maddening pain that makes me tremble
kowaresou na nakushisou na houseki da
It's like a fragile gemstone that could be easily lost
kuraberareru koto nado ubawareru koto nado nai
There's nothing to compare it to and it can't be stolen
kimi wa kimi de ii, saa waratte misete
You should just be yourself, Now show me a smile
nani mo kangaezutomo soko ni riyuu ga nakutomo
Even you don't think, Even if there is no reason
sore koso ga subarashii hajimari
This is a wonderful beginning
saa, yoake da
Now, dawn is about to break
gozen reiji akari kieta machi
At midnight, in a city where the lights are out
furikaereba sasou black night town
I look back and it beckons me Black Night Town
Those snakes are sensing
exactly where we are.
Snakes perceive body heat
and smell with their tongues.
You've studied a lot!
You're like a snake expert now.
皆様　お変わりございませんか？
Of course I did.
In order to take down Orochimaru!
美空ひばりです。
I'm no longer a snake...
では最後まで　ごゆっくり→
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Sibling Tag Team"
お楽しみください。
I am now a dragon!
『木曜８時のコンサート
名曲！　にっぽんの歌』。
２時間スペシャル！